iluvdressup.com 2013-05-21

# PRIVACY POLICY - iLuvDressUp.com - Dress up games

|  | 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

ILuvDressUp is committed to providing an entertaining, fun and educational service. iluvdressup.com is a property of ILuvDressUp. We respect the privacy concerns of visitors to iluvdressup.com.

**Information we collect and how we use it**

On your visit to our website there is certain information that we collect from traffic references of hosting servers and from cookies.

From traffic references of hosting servers – every time you visit a website, there is certain information you make available for collection such as IP address, time of visit, location, internet domain, type of browser and operating system used to access our site, pages you visit, if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website etc . We, like other operators, collect this information and use it for visitors’ statistics and to improve our services to you.

From Cookies – the sole purpose of cookies is to enhance your online experience. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer by Web sites. Through your Web browser, cookies are only used by the Web site that wrote the cookie. Data stored in a cookie from ILuvDressUp is only accessible by the ILuvDressUp Web site. This information enables us to run our affiliate programs, allows customized advertising, lets you automatically sign in when you visit ILuvDressUp, and offers other operational site activities. Most of browsers are set to accept cookies. But if you prefer, you can reset your browser so as to let you know whenever you receive a cookie or even to refuse cookies. However, you should know that some parts of ILuvDressUp website can only be normally seen if your browser allows cookies.

If you decide to create an account on our website, the information we collect is your email address in order for us to be able to communicate with you regarding your account and to send you notifications when necessary or our newsletter.

Your username, e-mail address, and password (needed for your registration) will be used to uniquely identify you as a member on ILuvDressUp Web site. We may use or display your username for the purposes of rankings, competitions or sweepstakes, chat identification, or game high scores. We may also collect other identifying information through voluntary means (such as Location, website, personal message etc) that will show up on your Profile.

ILuvDressUp will not share your information with anyone. The only exception shall be in the event that disclosure of information is required by law enforcement or other government officials in connection with investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or that may expose you or us to legal liability. 

**Collection of information and Third-Party sites and Sponsors**

It is important that you understand that advertisers or Web sites that link to a ILuvDressUp site may collect personal information about you. The Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of other advertisers or Web sites.   
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).   

Google Adsense 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on GirlGames4u website. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on your visit to GirlGames4u site and other sites on the Internet. 
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie or change your preferences by visiting the google ads preferences page [here](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

**Chat and Messaging**  
ILuvDressUp may choose to operate message boards and/or chat areas where users can exchange ideas and communicate with one another. When posting to a message board or chat area, it is important for you to understand that the information is being made publicly available in an online environment. Any information posted is the sole responsibility of the individual user. This is why we recommend not sharing your personal data such as real name or address.  
**Security**  
All data that we collect is stored on one or more database servers. We are taking any reasonable precaution to secure the data, but you have to understand that the internet is not 100% safe and we cannot guarantee the safety of your information. All this kind of transmission whatsoever is made on your own risk.   
**Links to Other Sites**  
Our website has links to partners and other sites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.   
**Parental review  
**You may review or request to have deleted any information your child has submitted to us. You may also request that we not collect any personal information about your child in the future. To do this, send a written request including your child's email address for verification to admin@iluvdressup.com

**Email Opt-Out**  
When you sign up as a ILuvDressUp user you agree to allow us to communicate with you via e-mail about news, games, special offers, and events. Any e-mail we send to you (not more than one a month) will contain information about opting-out of any further mailings, which will be possible only by closing your account. To do so, please email us at admin@iluvdressup.com from the same email address you used to register.

**AGREEMENT WITH iluvdressup POLICIES**  
By using this site, you signify your assent to the ILuvDressUp Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use ILuvDressUp site. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check the policy each time you use our web site to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our privacy policy will indicate the date it was last updated.  
  
---|---
